[BOYD] Previously on From.
What the fuck?
[JIM] Kenny! You gotta come down here!
There's enough food here to feed
everybody in the entire town!
You think this place can't break you?
Let's see.
- [TIAN-CHEN SCREAMING]
- [BOYD SHOUTING]
[JADE] You were in the barn
with her with those things.
How are you still alive?
They wanted me to watch.
- Kenny.
- Wait. Where's... where's my mom?
- Bud. I'm s...
- No! Stop! Just stop.
[CRYING]
- [BOYD] We need more information.
- [ELLIS] Yeah.
[BOYD] I'm gonna need your
help with something tomorrow.
With what?
We're gonna catch one
of these fucking things.
[DONNA] You're gonna have a baby
that you were told you could never have!
With all you've seen.
you can't wrap your
head around a miracle.
[MARIELLE] You're severely malnourished.
We really just need to
get you eating again.
Are those the crops?
Yeah. We figured we'd
try composting them.
see if we can't get
the soil turned around.
Mmm.
[SMASHING]
Jade?
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
You ready to tell me
what's going on with you?
Still kinda working it out for myself.
Do you remember the bracelet I made you?
You're saying you found a bracelet
- that's similar to the one you made?
- No. no. no. no. no. It's not similar.
That is the bracelet.
It's impossible.
[VICTOR] Visit the bottle tree.
My mother said this one
would take her to the tower.
to the children.
[HENRY] Miranda started seeing things.
She painted everything she saw.
She said it was like she'd been chosen
to free the children.
I guess you've been chosen now. too.
When Thomas died. you
and Mom fell apart.
and there was no one there for Ethan.
I need you to get your shit together.
Okay.
[RINGING]
Hello?
[BOY] Dad? It's Thomas.
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Daddy. are you there?
You are not my son.
[BOY] Why did you let Mommy go?
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Why did you want her to die?
Stop it!
Is it because you
didn't love her anymore?
[STATIC CRACKLING]
What do you want?
[BOY] To help. You need help. Daddy.
Stop calling me that.
[BOY] You should be
watching Julie and Ethan.
You shouldn't let them play
outside so close to dark.
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Daddy. are you there?
[CLANGING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING FAINTLY]
[BELL CONTINUING TO CLANG]
Ethan!
Julie!
Ethan! Julie!
[BELL CONTINUING TO CLANG]
Ethan!
Julie!
What?
What are you doing?
Feeding the animals!
Come on inside!
- Ethan!
- We're not done yet!
Hey. Ethan! I said right now! Come on!
- Jim!
- Huh?
[BOYD] You okay?
Yeah. You know. I'm...
I'm talking to my kids.
- Come on. Ethan.
- [SHEEP BLEATING]
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
- We're coming!
It's gonna be dark soon.
I know.
- They okay?
- [JIM] Yeah.
Sorry.
Things are getting worse
around here. aren't they?
Yeah.
["QUE SERA. SERA (WHATEVER
WILL BE. WILL BE)" PLAYS]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
- Synced and corrected by naFraC -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[BIRD CHIRPING DISTANTLY]
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
- [HENRY GRUNTING]
Wha?
[GRUNTING]
Uh. easy now. You'll cut yourself.
Ow! [GROANING]
Told you.
Were you down there all night?
You... You need to sleep.
[GROANING]
I need... I need answers.
There has to be something
in that basement.
in... in... in those
paintings that I'm missing.
I got some bandages in here somewhere.
Ah.
There we are.
Uh. no. Uh. you...
- Help me. please.
- Oh. no. no. It's all right.
So. that boy.
the... the one dressed in white.
you're saying that he lured you
up to the top of a lighthouse
and... and then pushed you out?
No. no. no. no. no. He didn't lure me.
I just went there because
of. you know. the children.
Children locked in the tower.
Yeah. You see. um...
[SIGHING] ... the tower
was actually a lighthouse.
and in order to get there.
I had to go through a tree.
Uh. Victor took me there.
He said his mother had gone off
to save the children as well.
the night she... she...
It's all right.
You can say it.
I. uh. accepted the fact that she died
a long. long time ago.
I thought they all had.
The fact that Victor is still
out there somewhere. it's...
[GLASS CLINKING]
Do you hear that?
[CLINKING CONTINUING]
Oh. the bottles.
Of course I hear them.
They're hanging. uh. on
a tree in the backyard.
Miranda used to call it the bottle tree.
[BIRD CALLING DISTANTLY]
[VICTOR] One. two. three.
[CHILDREN CHATTERING]
[VICTOR MURMURING]
[MURMURING]
[GRUNTING]
How do you even know
that this is possible?
Yeah. I don't.
but the talismans.
they keep those things from
getting into the houses.
Maybe it can keep them from
getting out of something.
Look. I get it. but we're
not talking about catching
a stray dog or a coyote. okay?
Those... those things. we
don't know anything about them.
Yeah. Well. maybe it's time we learned.
We can't just sit around
playing it safe anymore.
"Safe."
You spent one night out in the forest.
and it almost got you killed.
And then it almost got
everybody killed. but "safe."
Jim and Kenny spent the night
out in the forest. right?
And they came back with food.
and now. we have enough
food to feed everyone again!
The point is. it's not always
gonna work out the
way that we want it to.
but that doesn't mean
we can't take chances.
- I'm with you. okay?
- [DOOR OPENS]
I...
How'd it go with. uh.
Kenny and the others?
Fine. We all drew straws.
Dale threw a shit-fit.
and they all went on their way.
Should be down there by lunchtime.
And how did Kenny seem?
As good as can be expected.
Kristi's down there with them.
Good. Yeah.
All right. What the fuck's going on?
Okay. If you don't tell her. I will.
[SIGHING]
I wanna catch one of those things.
Sorry. What?
Those things show up every night.
every goddamn night.
and we still have no idea
what we're dealing with.
what they are. where they come from.
Boyd. we have been down this road.
You have already caught one.
No. I killed one.
That's different.
We need to learn about them.
We... We already know they talk.
so we catch one. We make it talk.
Oh. you're gonna make it talk.
How are you gonna do that?
You gonna torture it?
We have hit those things
point blank with shotguns.
and all it makes them do is smile!
They are not human.
Well. according to Kristi.
they were at some point!
Oh. and what part of that reassures you?
[SHOUTING] We gotta do
something. all right?
- Dad.
- You can't...
We gotta fucking do something.
How you gonna do it?
I am working on that.
Great.
Work harder.
Look.
I miss Tian-Chen. too.
and believe me. I do not
want us to not go out there
and get our pound of flesh.
But I do not want to
watch you get killed
because of some
half-baked. dumbass plan.
And don't you encourage him.
You got a baby on the way.
You have more to worry
about now than yourself.
- Dad...
- No.
All right.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Yep. Yep.
[SIZZLING]
- [SIZZLING]
- [CHATTERING]
What is that?
They divvied up the rest
of the cow this morning.
We got plenty. if you want some.
I don't think so.
Baby's not a meat-eater. huh?
I guess not.
[RETCHING]
♪
Well. that's terrifying.
I can't believe people
actually lived out here.
[DALE] Are we sure they were people?
I mean. look at this.
Just look at how they're positioned.
They may have been using them
the same way we use the talismans.
warding off evil spirits.
Oh. that's much more comforting.
Whatever happened. it
was a long time ago.
We have people back in
town who are hungry now.
So. uh. all right. Jim and I pulled
and gathered as much as
we could before we left.
It's up in that shack over there.
So. let's get. uh.
get Dale. Jade. Roger.
You guys can get started there.
The rest of us will go forage
whatever else we can find.
- Let's go! Wasting daylight!
- Great.
- [KRISTI] Careful.
Let's just walk right
past the scary voodoo tower
and go sort some veggies.
I did the best I could
with what we had left.
Good news is. when Kenny and the others
get back with the food.
we'll be off rations.
Won't that be good?
I guess so.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
I made some lunch. Do you want some?
No.
All right.
Who's gonna bury her?
What?
Who's gonna bury Mom?
Don't talk like that!
But...
what if her body's just
laying out there on the ground
with bugs and spiders?
Will her body just lay
there 'til it starts to rot?
Ethan.
But what if someone finds her someday.
and they don't know who she is
'cause all they find is bones?
- Stop!
- [CLATTERING]
God damn it! Stop!
- I'm sorry. I...
- Yeah.
Really gunning for
parent of the year. huh?
[PHONE RINGING]
[HENRY] Uh. Miranda was an artist.
She did all sorts of
installations all over town.
This was always one of her favorites.
You're saying there's
something like this
in that town you came from?
[TABITHA] No. This was different.
[SIGHING] It's not here.
What... What are you looking for?
The tree that Victor took me to
had some sort of.
like. opening. you know.
one that you can. like. step in.
and it will just take you somewhere.
So. you would step into the tree.
like teleporting?
It doesn't matter. It's just a tree.
Well. it's not the original.
if that matters.
- What?
- Well. like I said.
she... she did installations all over.
She liked this one so
much. she made a replica
for the... for the yard.
Said she wanted it to be close to her.
The original's in a
park a few towns over.
In fact...
What? In fact what?
Well. that was where we
dropped acid together.
You could say that tree
was where this all started.
Oh. my God. and how...
how far is it from here?
Thirty. 40 minutes.
Okay. You need to take
me there right now.
- You need to get some sleep.
- No. no. no. no. no.
You need to take me
there right now. Henry!
You're not gonna do
either of us any good
if you end up back in the hospital!
I'm not gonna... I'm not
gonna go to the hospital.
I just need to go to the
tree. Please take me! Let's go!
[MURMURING]
[KHATRI] So. is this some
part of your nefarious plan?
You really think you can
catch one of those things?
Maybe.
[HAMMERING]
Boyd. you've been here.
what? Year and half now?
Done pretty well by
most metrics. you know.
You kept most people alive
who'd otherwise be dead.
[HAMMERING]
Present company excluded. of course.
So why change things now?
Look around you.
Look at all the shit
that's happening lately.
You really gotta ask me that?
Well. at least you have
a solid plan. right?
Lure one of those things into a house.
Slap a talisman on the
outside of the door.
Trap it inside.
Next day. go over. Go inside.
Wander around the house.
searching for it room by
room until it jumps out
from somewhere and rips you to pieces.
Yeah. no. I can see how the
military trusted you to plan things.
You don't see it. do you?
Boyd. you can't even see what's
staring you right in the face.
Which is?
[KHATRI] Those things said
they wanted to break you.
and that means they
wanted to change you.
So far. so good. because
the Boyd I knew would
never do something
this colossally stupid.
Yeah. well. the Boyd
you knew got you killed.
[CHUCKLING]
You know. you might
wanna get down off of
that cross of yours every now and then.
- You know that?
- You know. fuck you. man.
I died because I was
trying to help people.
Tian-Chen. she died because
she was trying to help people.
You have any idea how arrogant it is
to diminish that sacrifice
by making this all about you?
But I really like your fancy art.
It's nice.
It's a memory board.
The graveyard has no markers.
no headstones. just bodies.
Probably bodies buried
all over the place.
We should have a place for their names.
Your name. Tian-Chen's.
You know. I think better
when I work with my hands.
so leave me the fuck alone. huh?
[GRUNTING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING OUTSIDE]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi.
Hello.
Do you need something?
Yes.
Do you want to come in?
So. what can I help you with?
What is that?
My brother made it for me.
I don't think I'll ever be
able to put it back together. but...
I like to try.
Do you have a bedspread?
Yeah. I have a few upstairs. Why?
We need to build a fort.
Then I'm gonna tell a story.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
It's Tillie.
Can I come in?
Um. I'm really not
feeling great right now.
I used to lick eggshells.
When I was pregnant with my first.
I used to lick the inside of eggshells.
Yep. Um. I couldn't...
stand the sight or the
smell of my favorite foods.
but crack an egg and leave
the shell on the counter.
I would even sneak 'em from the garbage
when my husband wasn't looking.
It started. um.
somewhere in my second trimester.
Lasted three weeks
and... and then stopped
mysteriously as it began.
Whatever's going on.
I promise it'll pass.
[SIGHING]
Yeah. maybe.
[CRYING]
It's okay.
I can't...
I can't talk to anyone.
You know what they do here.
I'm afraid that they would think...
And Ellis. he's so...
He's happy again.
actually happy.
And he's... he's working so hard.
trying so hard to be encouraging.
and I can't...
Can't what?
I can't tell him how scared I am.
What if there's something
wrong with the baby?
What if...
Every first-time mother
has these feelings.
I'm not supposed to be a mom.
I was never supposed to be one!
I'm not...
I was never supposed
to be able to conceive.
and yet. somehow. here...
I just want to know if
the baby's gonna be okay.
Well. then. let's find out.
Uh. it's not locked.
Okay.
- [ENGINE STARTING]
- ["BLUE" PLAYING ON STEREO]
It does that sometimes.
That tape's been stuck
in there for years.
"Blue" was Miranda's favorite song.
♪ Blue ♪
Tabitha?
You okay?
Yeah. It's... it's just
mine and my husband's song.
- Small world.
- ♪ Songs are like tattoos ♪
♪ You know I've been to sea before ♪
♪ Crown and anchor me ♪
I'm telling you. it was rigged.
Donna knew exactly who was
gonna draw the short straws.
Wouldn't kill you to
give us a hand. you know!
Fucking guy.
Guy's been losing his shit lately.
Yeah. no kidding.
Dead weight out here.
If you're gonna whisper.
you should try actually whispering.
Look. Everyone here is
having a hard time. you know.
It's not just you.
We're all stuck here.
and you walk around like some big shot
thinks he's smarter than everybody else
because you had some
rinky-dink company back home.
Oh. isn't it such a tragedy
that you're stuck here
while the rest of us...
[SHOUTING] Oh. will
you shut the fuck up?
You have no idea what
I've been through here.
no idea what I have seen!
So why don't we just... Ah.
Where are you going?
None of your fucking business!
Asshole.
Fucking guy.
None of your fucking business. Dale.
Ah.
[PULLING ZIPPER]
[MOANING]
[GRUNTING. SNIFFLING]
Huh.
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYING]
♪
[YELPING]
Get the fuck off me!
[SHOUTING] The hell's wrong with you?
Oh. Fuck this!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KRISTI] I'm pretty sure
that one might be full.
Yeah. We gotta make sure we bring back
as much as possible this first trip.
Kenny?
Kenny. look at me.
What?
Look. I can't even begin to imagine
what you're going through right now.
and I'm not gonna pretend like
I know the magic words
that are just somehow...
Where's your bag?
What?
Your bag.
the one you're supposed to
be putting crops in. Is it full?
Is that why you came out
here? To play nursemaid?
No. Kenny. I came out here
because I care about you.
That's great. Why don't
you care about me while
you do your fucking job?
Because we have two hours left.
and if we don't bring back
as much food as possible...
[DALE] You can't just leave.
I can do whatever the fuck I
want. and right now. I wanna go.
- Hey! What's going on?
- I'm going back to town!
Uh. Jade. you're never gonna
make it back before dark.
Well. I'm sure as fuck not staying here!
Let's all just take a breath. okay?
I played along with the
whole "Let's draw straws
to see who gets the food" bullshit.
- I came out here to help!
- Okay.
I don't like it here.
Who the fuck likes it anywhere?
It's a forest full of nightmares!
No. This is different.
This is diff... Look.
I wanna help. I do. okay?
I wanna help. but I...
I'll be more helpful back in town.
Hey. hey. hey. hey! You're
not gonna make it back to town.
Okay? You might not even make
it back to the talisman hut.
so just breathe. okay?
I'll make it if I run.
[KENNY] Just stop. Okay. Stop. Stop.
We have shelter here.
We have... we have talismans here.
and we need this food.
Jade. if we go back
to town empty-handed.
people starve.
Good luck.
- Jade!
- [KENNY] He's right.
If he hurries. he'll probably
make it back to the talisman hut
before sundown.
- Jade!
- [KENNY] Kristi!
[KRISTI] Jade. hold on!
You're going the wrong way!
- Jade!
- [SCOFFING]
Kristi!
[KRISTI] Jade. just hold on!
You don't even know where you're going!
Will you just stop for two seconds
- and think about what you're doing?
- Oh. trust me. I've done nothing
but think about what I'm doing!
I shouldn't be out here! I
should be back at the bar.
trying to figure out how to...
- Ah! Fuck!
- Kristi!
- Ah!
Ah! My foot...
- Hey! Fuck! Get... get off her!
- [GRUNTING]
- What the fuck did you do?
- What the hell?
It's not his fault! Just get
this fucking thing off of me!
- [DALE] Uh...
- [KRISTI GROANING]
There should be a release
somewhere. I don't know.
- Ow!
- Yes.
[KRISTI] Get this fucking thing off.
[JADE] Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
[KRISTI GROANING]
[KENNY] You're okay. Breathe.
- [GROANING]
- What the fuck?
Okay. I got it.
- You're okay.
- [KRISTI GROANING]
- [SNAPPING]
- [JADE SHOUTING]
- [KRISTI SHOUTING]
- Oh. fuck.
[KRISTI GROANING]
How's this?
Looks good to me.
Why don't you take all these in the back
and get them cleaned?
Okay.
Hey. little man.
Hi. Sheriff.
And what are you guys up to?
[ETHAN] We're just making
sure everything's clean
and put away the way
Tian-Chen would like it.
Oh. wow. That's really...
I'm sure she appreciates that.
I hope so.
[DOOR SWINGING]
Came down here to get
one of the big pots
for soup for Colony House.
and when I got here.
I found him cleaning.
Poor kid.
He's had so much to deal with already.
And what about you?
How you doing?
[SCOFFING]
Aside from trying to process
everything that's happened recently.
including how a nursery rhyme
my grandmother told me somehow...
[SIGHING]
I... I don't know how I'm
doing. if I'm being honest.
- Do you?
- [SIGHING]
It's been a rough stretch.
Is it always like this?
Does it get worse?
I mean. well. if I'm being honest.
I don't know.
But... but I do know
that no matter what
this place throws at us.
we're gonna win. all right?
No matter what happens here.
we are going to find our way home.
What if there isn't one?
Well. of course there is.
There's a way here. right?
If there's a way here.
there's a way home.
You don't know that.
You just hope there is.
Tian-Chen thought she was
going home. and so did my mom.
Hey. we are not giving
up on your mom. okay?
Maybe you should.
[DOOR SWINGING]
Yeah.
- [KENNY GRUNTING]
- [KRISTI GROANING]
- [MEN GRUNTING]
- I'm sorry.
- [DALE GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
This thing must have been
here for decades at least.
It's a good thing. too.
'cause all that rust and crap
- probably saved your foot.
- Lucky me.
Let's see if I can wedge this in there.
- Okay. Just back up. Back up.
- I'm just trying to help.
You've helped! Gimme that.
You wanna go back to town.
go! Get the fuck outta here.
Kenny. we gotta get
this thing off her leg
before the sun goes down!
Really. Jade? Thanks!
Get the fuck outta here!
Enough! This is nobody's fault.
so just cut the shit and
let's figure this out!
Why don't we just break the chain?
At least then we could get her inside.
- Break it with what?
- I don't know. smart guy.
You're supposed to be the genius.
[KRISTI GROANING]
[KENNY] Sorry. I'm sorry.
[CRACKING]
- [SNAPPING]
- [SHOUTING]
- [KRISTI GROANS]
- [KENNY] Sorry.
- Fuck!
We need something that's
gonna give us more leverage.
All right. we need...
[CROWS CAWING IN DISTANCE]
You. come with me.
What?
Just don't do anything
until we get back!
[GROANING]
[CHATTERING]
I know they're here somewhere.
Poor thing's exhausted.
I'm glad he's finally getting some rest.
Ah. Here they are.
Those what I think they are?
They are if you think
they're tarot cards.
You can't be serious.
Oh. You wanna know if
your baby's all right?
These here are gonna tell us.
This was a bad idea.
Hey! Where are you going?
Where am I going?
I opened up to you.
I confided in you. I...
You know what? Your whole
kooky. batty Tillie shtick
is fine in most circumstances.
but how dare you?
Now. hold on a second.
Is that what you think of me?
Kooky. batty Tillie.
just goofing around about
something this important to you?
Is that what you think of me?
I don't know.
I don't know anything
about you. Look. Just...
Now so. you don't believe.
That's fine.
but before you saw
that tree in the road.
I'll bet you didn't believe
in half the stuff we see here
every day and night. did you?
These things played a
pretty big role in my life
at a pretty critical juncture.
I just want to share that with you.
These cards were given to
me by a gal named Gertie.
She was in the same
hospice care as my husband.
[SIGHING]
She did a reading for
me after he passed.
Shuffle. please.
I thought that it was
a bit silly at the time.
but now I realize that those cards...
told me about my cancer.
told me about this place.
maybe not in so many words. but...
the signs were all there
if I'd known how to read them.
Please?
- Thank you.
- Do you now know how to read them?
Yeah. a lot better than I was before.
[SIGHING]
Ask them a question.
And let's see what they answer.
The worst thing that could happen
is you feel a bit silly once we're done.
Is my baby okay?
Let's see what the cards have to say.
[BANGING. CAWING]
What was that?
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [CROW CAWING]
- [WOMAN SCREAMING]
Ah!
[MAN] Jesus Christ!
This is a really bad idea.
There's nothing else strong
enough to pry that trap open.
You really wanna start pulling apart
the ancient tower of holy scary shit?
I'm sure whoever built it won't mind.
[GRUNTING]
Oh. Jesus. Fuck!
- Where the hell are they?
- Kenny. listen to me.
Yeah.
If this goes bad...
Hey. stop. stop. You're
gonna be fine. okay?
- Okay. Ken...
- We still have
- plenty of daylight left.
- Kenny!
Enough. okay?
We're gonna get you out of this
thing. and you're gonna be fine.
Boyd told me what your mom said.
No matter what happens
here. you'll never be alone.
Do you understand me?
You'll never be alone. okay?
You're gonna be fine.
I know.
Just tell me you heard what I said.
- Just tell me you understand.
- Okay. Okay.
I heard you. I understand that...
Where have you been? Let's go!
Getting us some leverage!
Okay. Here we go.
- Get behind her.
- [KENNY] Yeah. yeah.
Get on that side. Okay.
As soon as this opens up.
you pull her out. okay?
Ready? Okay. Here we go.
- [KENNY] Okay.
- And pull!
- [KRISTI GROANING]
- [KENNY] You okay? Open!
[SHOUTING]
[JADE] Pull! Pull!
- [KRISTI SHOUTING]
- Shit.
[KRISTI GROANING]
- What? Are you good?
- [STAMMERS] My ankle.
- It's dislocated.
- What? What?
- We have to reset it.
- [KENNY] Okay.
Ow! Okay.
Hold my foot. Kenny.
Dale. I need you behind me.
Jade. I need you to
hold on to my other foot.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
- Okay.
Kenny. keep your one hand
above... above my foot
and the other under my ankle.
[KRISTI GROANING]
Okay? All right.
[MENACING MUSIC PLAYS]
♪
Jade! Hey!
- Focus. Okay?
- Oh. yeah.
All right. Okay. You with me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Okay.
One. two. three!
- [SNAPPING]
- [KRISTI SCREAMING]
- You okay?
- [SCREAMING]
- [KENNY] Are you okay?
- [KRISTI] Ah!
- [KENNY] You good?
- [KRISTI] Fuck.
- [KENNY] Yeah?
- [KRISTI GROANING]
- [KENNY] You okay?
- [KRISTI] Christ.
- [KENNY] All right. Let's. uh...
- Ah!
Let's get her back to camp.
It's gonna be dark soon.
Yeah. yeah.
Okay. Here we go. Ready?
- Ah. fuck!
- Let's go that way.
- Go. go. go.
- Ah. fuck!
- Watch where you step.
- [KRISTI SCREAMING]
[CHATTERING OUTSIDE]
[BUZZING]
[BUZZING CONTINUING]
[BUZZING BECOMING LOUDER]
[YELPING]
Hey.
[GRUNTING]
It's just me.
Did you. uh...
What's going on?
Uh... [CHUCKLING]
Nothing. I... I thought...
- Hey. are you all right?
- Yeah.
The other day with the animals...
What the fuck do you want?
Huh?
I was thinking...
maybe we switch tonight.
Switch what?
[BOYD] Accommodations.
You take the sheriff's station.
I'll take the bus.
Why?
Because I wanna watch our friends
when they come out of the woods tonight.
see what they're up to.
You wanna watch. huh?
Yeah.
How come?
Well. I think it's time
we change things up a
little bit around here.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm just... I'm just
a little carsick. That's all.
How much further?
Uh. it's just down the road.
There should be some crackers
in the glove compartment there.
Might settle your stomach.
Okay.
Where did you get this?
Uh. Miranda made that for me. so...
What's wrong?
Uh. I'm so stupid.
I'm so stupid. I'm so stupid.
I... I'm so stupid.
- This... this can't be real.
- Hmm?
This can't be real.
I...
[STAMMERS] I went through a magic tree
and traveled to a lighthouse
like something out of a fairytale.
I wake up in the hospital
that just happens to be here.
You just happen to be here.
No. No. no. no. no. no. no. no. no.
No. no.
No. but this... this was your mistake.
- This was too far.
- I... I don't understand.
What... What does
that have to do with...
I made this for my husband
a long time ago. and he lost it.
And then I found this... in the diner.
Okay.
We're not really in
Camden. Maine. are we?
[CRYING]
What?
It's just more of this place.
torturing me. punishing me. right?
What are you talking about?
- You need to pull over right now!
- What? Where...
You need to pull over right now. please!
Okay. All right. all
right. I'm pulling over.
I don't understand. Look. I... I...
What happens if I get out of the car?
- Get out of...
- What happens
if I refuse to play along?
Do... Do I end up back
at the hospital again?
Does it start all over?
I... I don't know what's
happening right now.
but... but the park. the tree.
it's just down the street!
- No. no. no. no. no.
- Please!
- No. no. no. no.
- You can't do this!
You can't just show up at my door.
say the things you've said.
tell me my son is alive!
- No. no. no.
- My boy. that he's out there!
- No!
- And then you just decide
that you're gonna give up on that!
- I can't.
- No. no! No!
No. no! God!
- We're going!
- [ENGINE ROARING]
[HORN HONKING]
- [CRASHING]
- [HENRY] Ah!
[SIREN WAILING]
[AIR HISSING]
Where am I? [GROANING]
Don't sit up.
- [TABITHA] Jim?
- You're okay.
You're okay. You were in a car accident.
Oh. my God.
So you're the lady with the lunchbox.
[GROANING]
What?
[POLICE OFFICER] It was in
your report at the hospital.
Oh. my God. Is he okay?
He's having a little trouble.
but we're monitoring him.
- Okay.
- [OFFICER] The hospital staff
was worried about you.
We've had patrol cars
on the lookout for you
ever since you ran out
the other day. but
you're gonna be all right.
No. no. no. I... I... I don't
wanna go to the hospital.
- You need to lie still.
- [OFFICER] Ma'am.
- [TABITHA] Please. I'm fine.
- [PARAMEDIC] Ma'am. please.
[TABITHA] Just stop and let me out.
[KNOCKING] Hey. everything all right?
There's a tree in the
middle of the road.
[GASPING]
No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
No. no. no. Oh. my God.
♪
[END THEME PLAYS]
- Synced and corrected by naFraC -
- www.addic7ed.com -